翻译、时间轴、压制：up主
I'm asking for the vote of every African-American citizen struggling in our country today
我希望每个在我国奋斗而且还期待一个不同且更好未来的非洲裔美国人
who wants a different and much better future.
向我投票
It's time for our society to address some honest and very very difficult issues.
现在该让我们的社会处理这些确实存在而且十分艰巨的问题了
The Democratic Party has failed and betrayed the African-American community.
民主党在这些问题上失败了 而且背叛了非裔美国人
Democratic crime policies, education policies and economic policies
民主党的安全政策 教育政策 经济政策
have produced only more crime, more broken homes and more poverty.
不过只是产生了更多的犯罪 家庭悲剧和贫穷
The African-American community has been taken for granted for decades
数十年来 非裔美国人群体被民主党想当然地当作票仓
by the Democratic Party and look how they're doing.
瞧瞧他们到底在干啥
It's time to break with the failures of the past.
是时候与过去的失败决裂了
I want to offer Americans a new and much better future.
我想给美国人带来全新且更好的未来
It's time for ruled by the people not ruled for the special interest
如今的国家应该由人民
which we have right now.
而不是现在的那些特殊利益集团来统治
To every voter in Milwaukee, to every voter living in the inner city
对于每个住在密尔沃基的选民 每个在市中心贫民区居住的选民
or every forgotten stretch of our society,
亦或是每个被遗忘的社会角落
I'm running to offer you a much better future, a much better job
我为你们争取一个更好的未来 工作
and a much higher wage.
和更高的工资而竞选
The Democratic party is taking the votes of African-Americans for granted.
民主党把非裔美国人的选票当作囊中之物
They've just assume they'll get your support and done nothing in return for it.
他们觉得自己被你们钦定了 而且无需做任何事来对此进行回报
They've taken advantage of the African American citizen.
他们不过是在利用非裔美国公民
It's time to give the Democrats some competition for these votes
该让民主党在拿这些选票的时候尝尝竞争的滋味了
and it's time to rebuild the inner cities of America
与此同时也该重塑美国的贫民区了
and to reject the failed leadership of a rigged political system
也是时候拒绝傀儡政治体制的失败领导了
and that's what it is. It's a rigged system.
就是这样 这确实是个傀儡体制
I'm running to listen to your voice,
我为了听到你们的声音而竞选
to hear the cries for help from so many people in our nation.
甚至是国内那么多人求救的呼声
The quiet voices in our society not the loudest Demonstrators need to have their demands heard.
我们社会中最沉默的一部分需要把他们的需求让别人知道 而不是最喧闹的民主党人
We reject the bigotry of Hillary Clinton
我们对希拉里的偏见说不
which panders to and talks down to communities of color
这偏见指的是它根据人种来进行煽动和贬损
and sees them only as votes that's all they care about.
而且把选民只当作他们唯一关心的选票使用
Not as individual human beings worthy of a better future.
而不是把选民当作一个追求更好未来的独立个体看待
They have taken advantage.
他们已经这么利用过了
Hillary Clinton backed policies are responsible for the problems in the inner cities today
希拉里的反动政策是现在贫民区问题的来源
and a vote for her is a vote for another generation of poverty, high crime and lost opportunities.
所以如果投票给她就意味着资磁又一代的贫穷 高犯罪率和失业
I care too much about my country to let this happen.
我实在不希望这种情况在我们国家发生
The Democratic Party has run nearly every inner city in this country for 50 years
民主党在我国几乎所有的贫民区统治了50多年
and run them into financial ruin, virtually every single one.
差不多把他们都统治到了经济崩溃
They ruined the schools.
他们摧毁了教育
They've driven out the jobs.
他们挤走了工作
They have tolerated a level of crime no American should consider acceptable,
他们容忍着任何一个美国人都不能接受的高犯罪率
worse than many third world countries, so bad that people don't want to even report on them.
甚至比许多第三世界国家还要高 以至于人们都习以为常
The real numbers are beyond belief.
这些真实的数据超乎想象
Violent crime has risen 17% in America's 50 largest cities last year.
在去年美国50个最大的城市中 暴力犯罪案件数目上涨了17%
Homicides are up more than sixty percent in Baltimore alone.
仅仅在巴尔的摩 凶杀案件数目上涨了超过60%
There up more than fifty percent in Washington, D.C..
而在华盛顿特区 涨幅超过50%
This is the future offered by the policies of Hillary Clinton and her friends,
这就是希拉里和她的朋友们的政策带来的未来
more poverty more crime and basically just more of the same.
更多的贫穷和犯罪还有基本上都差不多的东西
The future she offers is the most pessimistic thing I could possibly imagine.
我基本上能想象到 她带来的未来可以说是最可悲的东西
It's time for a different future here is what I'm proposing.
而我现在计划的未来正与此不同
First on immigration.
首先是移民问题
No community in this country has been hurt worse by Hillary Clinton's immigration,
由于希拉里的移民政策和她的其他政策
and all of her policies than the African-American community.
我国的非洲裔美国人群体的受损程度超过了其他所有的群体
And she considers them a guaranteed vote.
而她以为获得这些选票可以不费吹灰之力
Now she is proposing to print instant work permits for millions of illegal immigrants to come in
目前她规划着要让数百万非法移民进入我国并立刻提供工作许可
and take everybody's job including low-income African-Americans.
同时夺走每个人的工作 其中包括低收入的非洲裔美国人群体
Not right. Not gonna happen.
不可以 这不会发生
I will fight to ensure that every American is treated equally, protected equally and honored equally.
为了保证每个美国人被公平地对待 保护和尊重 我将不断努力
We will reject bigotry and hatred and oppression in all of its many ugly forms
同时拒绝任何形式的丑恶的偏见 仇恨和压迫
and seek a new future of security prosperity and opportunity.
并且追求一个安全 繁荣和有机会的全新未来
A future built on our common culture and values as one American people.
一个建立在整体美国人民这样共同文化价值观之上的未来
Our job is to make life more comfortable
我们的工作是为了让生活更加舒适
for the African-American parent who wants their kids to be able to safely
也是为了让非洲裔美国人的家长希望他们的孩子能安全地
safely walk the streets and walk to school
安全地在街上走 亦或是安全地上学
or the senior citizen waiting for a bus
也可能是等待公交车的长者
or the young child walking home from school.
也可能是从学校回家的小孩
For everyone violent protester there are a hundred moms and dads and kids on the same city block
对于每个抗议暴力的人 每个城市小区里都有成百上千的家庭
who just want to be able to sleep safely at night.
不过只是想晚上睡觉时安全一些
They want safety.
他们想要安全
We are going to put students and parents first.
我们将会把学生和家长放在第一位
Hillary Clinton would rather deny opportunities to millions of young African-American children
不过希拉里只会把机会从成千上万的非洲裔美国人的小孩那儿夺走
just so she can curry favor with the education bureaucracy
这样只为了能讨好教育官僚
which is very big and a lot of votes.
这也是一个巨大的票仓
注：A charter school is a U.S. and Canadian term for a school that receives government funding but operates independently of the established public school system in which it is located. Charter schools are an example of alternative education.
根据知乎/question/21810104上的回答，大概是服务少数族裔的一批特许学校。
I am going to allow charter schools to thrive
我将推动特许学校的发展
and help young kids get on the American ladder of success
并帮助小孩搭上美式成功的阶梯
a good education and a good paying job.
一个好的教育和一个高薪的工作
That's what they want.
这就是他们所想的
And I'm going to break up the gangs, the cartels and the criminal syndicates
接着我将打击黑帮 贩毒集团和犯罪团伙
terrorizing our neighborhoods all over the country and that includes Milwaukee.
威胁着全国上下的社区 其中包括密尔沃基
The reason you see the establishment
你们看到的那些建制派
and the establishment media lining up behind my opponent
还有那些站在我的对手后面的建制派媒体资磁着她
is because they are scared that you with your vote can take away their power
就是因为他们害怕你们的选票会剥夺他们的权力
and return it to your family and to your community.
同时这权力就会回归你们的家庭和社区
And they are scared and they have no idea how many people on november eighth
他们畏惧着是因为他们完全搞不清楚到了十一月八号那天
are going to come out and vote.
会有多少人出来投票
My opponent asks her supporters to recite a three-word pledge.
我的对手要求她的支持者诵读一个三词诺言
Her pledge reads "I'm with her".
叫做“我和她一道”
I choose to recite a totally different pledge.
我选择一个与此完全不同的
My pledge reads "I'm with you, the American people".
叫做“美国人民 我和你们一道”
To every parent who dreams for their children,
对于每个为他们子女抱有梦想的家长
and to every child who dreams for their future,
和每个为自己未来有着期待的子女
I say these words to you tonight.
我今晚要对你们说
I'm with you.
我和你们一道
I will fight for you and I will win for you.
我会为你们而战 我会为你们而赢
Together we will make America strong again.
我们会一起让美国再次强大
We will make America safe again.
我们会让美国再次安全
And we will make America great again, greater than ever before.
同时我们会让美国再次伟大 而且比历史上任何一个时期都更伟大
Thank you and God bless you.Thank you.Thank you.
谢谢 上帝保佑你们 谢谢 谢谢